Kagiso Moepya



kagisomoepya19@gmail.com



0695473801



linkedin.com/in/kagiso-moepya-87818015a

Summary

I am a Software Development student at WeThinkCode_.

I first studied at the University of the Western Cape where I became a graduate in the field of Commerce, majoring in Information Systems (IS).

Experiencing university was an experience and a half because that is where I got to develop my love for programming which led me to where I am today, being part of WeThinkCode_.

In my journey, I have come to understand how my professions compliment each other and this is something which I would like to further explore on a larger scale.

Experience

Student Mentor

WeThinkCode

May 2022 - May 2022 (1 month)

Assist bootcamp students solve coding related problems and make them understand the content better, furthermore what is expected of them within specific challenges.

Information Systems 361 Tutor

University of the Western Cape Mar 2021 - Jul 2021 (5 months)

Information systems 242/244 tutor

University of the Western Cape Jan 2020 - Jan 2021 (1 year 1 month)

Examination Assistant

Northlink College
Dec 2019 - Dec 2019 (1 month)

Quantitative Skills for Commerce 131/132 tutor

University of the Western Cape Jan 2019 - Dec 2019 (1 year)

Examination Assistant

Ekurhuleni East College Nov 2018 - Dec 2018 (2 months)

Education

WeThinkCode

Higher National Diploma, Computer Software Engineering Sep 2021 - Jun 2023

University of the Western Cape

Bachelor of Commerce - BCom, Management Information Systems, General

2018 - 2020

Major : Information Systems Minor : Financial Accounting

Skills

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Node.js • SASS • SQL • Figma (Software) • GitHub • Gitlab • Java • JavaScript • Python (Programming Language)